A Guide to the Additional Papers of Kevin Lynch, 2001-2007
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Additional Papers of Kevin Lynch 2001-2007
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
13881-a
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The collection was a gift of Kevin Lynch 2008 April 9.
Scope and Content
Major topics in this addition to the papers of the Charlottesville City Council member include City Council meetings, the Charlottesville Planning Commission, the utility rate report, the Route 250 interchange at McIntire Road, and the Virginia Municipal League.
Contents List
- Affordable Housing Issues, 2007 August, (8 items) (Box-folder 1:1)
- Calendars, 2008, (4 items) (Box-folder 1:2)
- Capital Improvement Plan Agenda, 2007 November 27, (6 items) (Box-folder 1:3)
- Capital Improvement Plan Meeting Power points, 2007 September-October, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:4)
- Capital Improvement Plan: Responses to Planning-Commission, 2007 December, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:5)
- Charlottesville Planning Commission Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 August 14, (13 items) (Box-folder 1:6)
- Charlottesville Planning Commission Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 September 11, (9 items) (Box-folder 1:7)
- Charlottesville Planning Commission Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 October 9, (10 items) (Box-folder 1:8)
- Charlottesville Planning Commission Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 November 13, [Folder 1 of 2] (7 items) (Box-folder 1:9)
- Charlottesville Planning Commission Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 November 13, [Folder 2 of 2] (5 items) (Box-folder 1:10)
- Charlottesville Planning Commission Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 December 11, (12 items) (Box-folder 2:1)
- Charlottesville's Housing Conditions and Problems, 2002-2007, (6 items) (Box-folder 2:2)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 August 6, (27 items) (Box-folder 2:3)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 September 4, (27 items) (Box-folder 2:4)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 September 17, (21 items) (Box-folder 2:5)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 October 1, (16 items) (Box-folder 2:6)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 October 15, (15 items) (Box-folder 2:7)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 November 5, (16 items) (Box-folder 3:1)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 November 19, (17 items) (Box-folder 3:2)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 December 3, (11 items) (Box-folder 3:3)
- City Council Agenda and Meeting Notes, 2007 December 17, (15 items) (Box-folder 3:4)
- City of Charlottesville: Budget History Notebook, 2007 November, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 3:5)
- City of Charlottesville: Construction Report, 2007 September, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 3:6)
- City of Charlottesville: Utility Rate Report, 2001-2002, [folder 1 of 3] (1 notebook) (Box-folder 3:7)
- City of Charlottesville: Utility Rate Report, 2003-2005, [Folder 2of 3] (1 notebook) (Box-folder 3:8)
- City of Charlottesville: Utility Rate Report, 2006, [Folder 3 of 3] (1 notebook) (Box-folder 3:9)
- City of Charlottesville: 2007 Comprehensive Plan, 2007, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 4:1)
- Construction Reports, 2007 July-December (Box-folder 4:2)
- Development of Building Blocks to Precise Ecological Flows for Rivanna River Watershed 2006 May, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 4:3)
- ED [Economic Development] News, 2007 May-September, (4 items) (Box-folder 4:4)
- Environmental Survey, 2007 October, (1 item) (Box-folder 4:5)
- Expenditure and Revenue Reports, 2006 November-2007 November, (4 items) (Box-folder 4:6)
- Flyers, miscellaneous, n.d., (7 items) (Box-folder 4:7)
- Guidelines for Public Video Surveillance: A Guide to Protecting Communities and Preserving Civil Liberties, 2007, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 4:8)
- Human Services Strategic Plan- Phase II: Background Data and Research and Identification of Priorities, 2007 July, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 4:9)
- Letter from Comprehensive Health Investment Project, 2007 December, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:1)
- Letter from Jefferson Area Board for Aging [JABA], 2007 November, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:2)
- Letters to the Mayor of Charlottesville, 2007 November, (3 items) (Box-folder 5:3)
- Meeting: Becoming a Green Community, 2007 September 6, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:4)
- Meeting: Code Enforcement, 2007 July 9, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:5)
- Meeting: Curriculum and Instruction Projects, 2007 June 15, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:6)
- Meeting: Downtown Design Guidelines, 2007 April 5, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:7)
- Meeting: Fostering 21st Century Skills, n.d., (1 item) (Box-folder 5:8)
- Meeting: Housing Work Session Follow-Up, 2007 June 5, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:9)
- Meeting: Long Term Financial Stability, Fiscal Year 2009, 2007 November 19, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:10)
- Metropolitan Planning Organization Policy Board Agendas, 2007 July-December, (6 items) (Box-folder 5:11)
- Pandemic Flu Planning Update, 2007 September, (7 items) (Box-folder 5:12)
- Partnership for Children: Annual Analysis, 2007 November, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 5:13)
- Petition for Housing Development, 2007, (1 item) (Box-folder 5:14)
- Project Status Updates, 2007 May-December, (6 items) (Box-folder 5:15)
- Regional Transit Authority (RTA) Plan Technical Reports, 2007 October, (3 items) (Box-folder 5:16)
- Rivanna River Basin Commission Agendas, 2007 April-June, (3 items) (Box-folder 5:17)
- Rivanna Solid Waste Authority Strategic Plan, 2007 November-December, (3 items) (Box-folder 6:1)
- Rivanna Water and Sewer Authority: Permit Support Document, 2006 June, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:2)
- Robert S. Smith Aquatic and Wellness Center: Preliminary Feasibility Study, 2007 October, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:3)
- Roofline: Piedmont Housing Alliance News, 2007 Summer, (1 item) (Box-folder 6:4)
- Route 250 Interchange at McIntire Road: Environmental Assessment, 2007 September, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:5)
- Route 250 Interchange at McIntire Road: Presentation to City Council, 2007 November 5, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:6)
- Route 250 Interchange at McIntire Road: Public Hearing List of Displays, 2007 November 1
- Route 250 Interchange at McIntire Road: Public Hearing Summary and Transcript, 2007 December, (3 items) (Box-folder 6:7)
- Route 250 Interchange at McIntire Road: Steering Committee Meeting, 2007 August 16, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:8)
- Route 250 Interchange at McIntire Road: Steering Committee Meeting, 2007 October 3, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:9)
- Sign Ordinance Amendments, 2007 July, (5 items) (Box-folder 6:10)
- US Route 29 Pedestrian Study, n.d., (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:11)
- Virginia Municipal League: Legislative Committee, 2007 September, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:12)
- Virginia Municipal League: 2008 Policy Statements, 2007 September, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:13)
- Year-End Adjustments: Fiscal Year 2006, 2006 December, (1 notebook) (Box-folder 6:14)